//Questions and Answers
const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'What is the word for cheese?',
        answers: [
            'Le fromage',
            'Le pain',
            'Le chocolat',
            'Le buerre'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Le fromage'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the word for milk?',
        answers: [
            'Le buerre',
            'Le pain',
            'Le fromage',
            'Le lait'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Le lait'
    },
    {
        question: 'How do you say hello?',
        answers: [
            'Bonjour!',
            'Au Revoir!',
            'Bonne Nuit',
            'Je m\'appelle'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Bonjour!'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the word for kiss?',
        answers: [
            'Chanter',
            'Ecouter',
            'Bisou',
            'Manger'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Bisou'
    },
    {
        question: 'The word \xE9toile means:',
        answers: [
            'Whistle',
            'Sing',
            'Star',
            'Love'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Star'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the word for butterfly?',
        answers: [
            'La Butterfrie',
            'Le Papillon',
            'Le Chat',
            'Doux'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Le Papillon'
    },
    {
        question: '"J\'aime ma soeur" means:',
        answers: [
            'I like soccer',
            'I like my sister',
            'I aim to please',
            'Jerry aims my sword'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'I like my sister'
    },
    {
        question: 'The word soleil means:',
        answers: [
            'Solar power',
            'Sun',
            'Sorry',
            'Sold'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Sun'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the capital of France?',
        answers: [
            'Washington',
            'Paris',
            'Versailles',
            'Chanter'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Paris'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the word for grapefruit?',
        answers: [
            'Le pamplemousse',
            'Le lionfruit',
            'Le camembert',
            'Le citronnade'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Le pamplemousse'
    }
];
